Kheel, Theodore W. Additional Files. 6021/010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Gateway Sporting Goods Co. TWK $25000 Loan, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- Gateway Sporting Goods Co. Sale of J.W. Carroll and Sons, Inc. Stock, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 24)
- Gateway sporting Goods Co. Bankruptcy Proceeding, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- George Meany Center for Labor Studies - National Labor college Proposal: School - to - Work - to - School, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  Aug
- George Meany Center for Labor Studies - National Labor College Foreign Affairs Pamphlet, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  Jan/Feb
- George Meany Center for Labor Studies - National Labor College Articles, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 28)
- George Meany Center for Labor Studies - National Labor college Miscellaneous, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 29)
- George Meany Center for Labor Studies - National Labor college Correspondence, Lane Kirkland Conference + Learning Center, 2003- 2005 (Box 35, Folder 30)
- George Meany Center for Labor Studies - National Labor College RE: Changing our World (Tom Watson), 2003 (Box 35, Folder 31)
- C. Leonard Gordon - RE: Immunotherapy, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 35, Folder 32)
- Gorewitz, Rubin RE: Igor Foundation, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 33)
- Personal File Henry George Greene, 1960-1961 (Box 35, Folder 34)
- Henry George Greene, Orders, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 35)
- Paid Bills A-L, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Paid Bills M-Z, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Daily Sheets (Phone Calls), 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  Oct 30, 1960 - Dec 29, 1961
- Cost Record - Blueprints Only, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  Jan
- Cassell Blueprint co. (Ridgway's) Invoices, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Cost Record - Ridgway's July thru Dec, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Cost Record - Ridgway's Jan thru June, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Ridgway's Invoices, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Paid Bills Albert Pfeiffer, Jr., 1961 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Paid Bills M-Z, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Mr. J.B. Raynes R + P Associates, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Paid Bills M to Z, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Paid Bills A-L, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Job Applicants, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Invoices (Professional Services ) Henry George Greene, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Paid Bills a-l, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Cost Record - Blue Prints Only, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Mr. Silverblatt Orders, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- O P Q, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Invoices (Professional Services), 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- M N, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- I J, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Goldenson, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- G H, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- E F, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Demov + Morris 1450 Broadway, New York 18, NY, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- W XYZ, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Paid Bills, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  A-L
- R S, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Mr. I.J. Feldman, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 30)
- A B, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 31)
- C D, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 32)
- Gobel, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 33)
- E/S Exterior St. Between E. 149th St. + E. 150th St. Bronx - Adolph Gobel, Inc., Correspondence, 1952-1959 (Box 36, Folder 34)
- General correspondence, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  March - July
- National Banquet Paid Bills, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 36)
- National Blueprint - Paid Bills, 1957-1959 (Box 36, Folder 37)
- Cost Record - blueprints Only, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 38)
- General correspondence out - Aug-Dec, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 39)
- Gregory, Raymond F., 2002 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Raymond F. Gregory, Esq., 1985-1986 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Gregory Raymond G., 1997 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Arthur Guiden, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Halpern, Samuel RE: Bear Stearns Fiduciary Services, Inc., 1987 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Harlem - Dowling Children's Service Dinner Correspondence and Memos, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Hastings - correspondence Sustainable Developments (Folder 1), 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Hastings - Correspondence Sustainable Developments (Folder 2), 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Hastings - correspondence Sustainable developments (Folder 3), 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Hastings - Correspondence Sustainable Developments (Folder 4), 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Hastings - Correspondence Sustainable Developments (folder 5), 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- shelly v. Eisenberg + Harbor at Hastings et al, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Right of Way Easement Agreement, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- FC Hastings v. East Shore Associates, 1997-1998 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- state of New York v. Hastings - Hastings v. Greenburgh, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Hastings RE: Weston Proposal, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Sustainable Development - Hastings on Hudson - ICF Kaiser, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- sustainable Development - Hastings on Hudson Riverkeeper Info, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Hastings RE: Community Preservations Corporation, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Hastings - Legal Research, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Hastings - Index of Documents, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Sustainable Development - Hastings on Hudson RE: Laura Reichler, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- The Kreisberg Group, Ltd., 1998 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Sustainable Development - Hastings on Hudson Hastings Purchase - Battle Fowler Statements, 1996-1998 (Box 37, Folder 24)
- sustainable Development - Hastings on Hudson Hastings Purchase - Plans, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- sustainable Development - Hastings on Hudson Hastings Purchase - Press Release, 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 26)
- Sustainable Development - Hastings on Hudson Hastings - Notes, 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- Sustainable Development - Hastings on Hudson Hastings - IRS Info, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Hempstead Realty Associates Limited Partnership Agreement, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 29)
- Hempstead Realty Associates - Bankruptcy, 1985-1986 (Box 37, Folder 30)
- Hempstead Realty Assoc. - Mortgage, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 31)
- Hickey, Kober, Incorporated Nationwide Legal Services, 1985-1989 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Higgins, Chester - NY Historical Society Correspondence, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Higgins, Chester Ethnic Demographic, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Higgins, Chester Flowers of Youth, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Higgins, Chester "Inside My Heart", 2002-2005 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Highway Action Coalition, 1971-1974 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Jack Hilton Incorporated RE: Chester Burger Matter, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Hirschfield, Desmond, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Hirschfield, Lord Desmond RE: Paintings, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Cronkite (interfaith Alliance), 1997 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffer's, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America local 445 and Food Packers, Cannery, and Miscellaneous Workers Union local 220, affiliated with the amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America AFL-, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffer's, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America local 445 and Food Packers, Cannery, and Miscellaneous Workers Union local 220, affiliated with the amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America AFL-, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffer's, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America local 445 and Food Packers, Cannery, and Miscellaneous Workers Union local 220, affiliated with the amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America AFL-, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffer's, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America local 445 and Food Packers, Cannery, and Miscellaneous Workers Union local 220, affiliated with the amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America AFL-, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  Copies and Drafts
- International Typographical Union Printers Home Telfare Communications, Inc., 1984 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Institute of Collective Bargaining + Group Relations, 1966-1975 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Institute of Collective Bargaining + Group Relations Financial Statements, 1975-1976 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- ICB Board Meeting Institute of Collective Bargaining + Group Relations, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  Aug 20 - Nov 11
- IZM, LLC, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Jones, Alex Miscellaneous, 1999-2000 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Kelly, James Arbitration File, 2001-2003 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- Kelly, James Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Kelly, James Legal Research, 2001-2002 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Kelly, James Resume, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- Kelly, James Notes, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Kelly, James Extra Copies, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Kelly, Commissioner Raymond, 1992-1994 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- TWKs Book Continued (Kheel on Labor Law) Kept to Conflict Res. (Folder 1), 1999-2002 (Box 38, Folder 28)
- TWKs Book - Continued (folder 2), 1998 (Box 38, Folder 29)
- Excerpt - The Keys to Conflict resolution (Kheel on Labor Law) (Box 38, Folder 30)
- TWK Book: Cartoons, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 31)
- TWK Book: Articles (Box 38, Folder 32)
- RE: Conflict Resolution On-Line Primer (Link Systems Int'l) Kheel on Labor Law-Book, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 33)
- Conflict Resolution Org (Kheel on Labor Law Book), 1999 (Box 38, Folder 34)
- NY Law Journal - book Review (Kheel on Labor Law - Keep to Conflict Res) TWK Book, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 35)
- Four Walls, Eight Windows Share Certificate, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 36)
- Four Walls, Eight Windows TWK: Contract w/ John Oakes, RE: Book (Box 38, Folder 37)
- TWK's Book Mailing Lists Material, 1997-1999 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- TKW Book: Reception/Invitation Letter, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Presidential Papers of John F. Kennedy (Newspaper Strike), 1963 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  March 2
- TWK's Book on Conflict Prevention + Resolution Drafts (Folder 1) (Box 39, Folder 4)
- TWK's Book on Conflict Prevention + Resolution Drafts (folder 2) (Box 39, Folder 5)
- TWK's Book on Conflict Prevention Resolution Drafts (Folder 3) (Box 39, Folder 6)
- TWK's Book on Conflict Prevention + Resolution Drafts (Folder $) (Box 39, Folder 7)
- TWK's Book on Conflict Prevention Drafts (Folder 5) (Box 39, Folder 8)
- TWK's Book on Conflict Prevention + Resolution Drafts (Folder 6) (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Correspondence with Peter Osnos TWK Book, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- TWK's Book / Files Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- TWK's Book Manuals and Publications, 1993-1995 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- TWK's Book Dispute Resolution Journal, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- TWK's Book AAA Publication: ADR in the Courts, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- TWK's Book RE AAA: Commercial Arbitration Rules, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- TWK's Book CPR Model ADR Procedures and Practices, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- TWK's Book Legal Research, 1990-1995 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- TWK's Book - Miscellaneous Articles + Quotes Prepared by TWK, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- TWK Book: Agreement with Charles Markham (Conflict Resolution), 1994-1997 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- TWK's Book - August + Corresp. w/ Charles Markham 1994-1997 + List of Files (folder 2) ADR, Total Approach to Conflict Prevention and Resolution (Box 39, Folder 20)
- TWK Book: Agreement w/ Sandra Goroff Mailly, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- TWK's Book (ADR), n.d. On Negotiations, Arbitration and Litigation of Disputes (Box 39, Folder 22)
- TWK's Book Info RE: Transit Negotiations, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- TWK's Book P S Study RE: Transit Negotiations, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- TWK Book - Materials and Relevant Articles (Folder 1) (Schachtman) (Box 40, Folder 1)
- TWK Book - Materials and Relevant Articles (folder 3) (Schachtman) (Box 40, Folder 2)
- TWK Book - Materials and Relevant Articles (folder 4) (Schachtman) (Box 40, Folder 3)
- TWK's Book w/ T. Shachtman - Media Interviews TWK's Career in NYC Affairs, 1945-1995 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- TWK's Book - (T Shachtman) Magazines, Journals, etc., Miscellaneous Materials (Folder 1) (Box 40, Folder 5)
- TWK's Book - (T. Shachtman) Books, 1964-1981 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- TWK's Book w/ T. Shachtman correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- twk'S Book w/ T Shachtman, n.d. Correspondence with Tom Shachtman (Box 40, Folder 8)
- TWK's Book w/ T. Shachtman n.d. Shachtman Memo (Box 40, Folder 9)
- TWK's Book w/ T. Shachtman Agreement w/ Tom Shachtman, 1994-1995 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- TWK's Book w/ T. Shachtman TWK's Career Notes, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- TWK Book: Legal Research incl. List of Kheel's Files, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Theodore W. Kheel Chronological Files, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Theodore W. Kheel Chronological File, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Theodore W. Kheel Chronological File, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Theodore W. Kheel Chronological File, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Theodore W. Kheel Chronological File, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Theodore W. Kheel chronological File, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Theodore W. Kheel Chronological File, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Theodore W. Kheel Chronological File, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Theodore W. Kheel Chronological File, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Theodore W. Kheel Chronological Files, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Theodore W. Kheel Chronological Files, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Theodore W. Kheel Chron File, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Theodore W. Kheel Chron File, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  Jan-Aug
- Theodore W. Kheel Chron file, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  Sept. - Dec.
- Theodore W. Kheel Chron File, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Kheel V. Ravitch RE: Redesignation as Impartial Arbitrator Correspondence w/ Mayor Koch, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Kheel v. Ravitch RE: Redesignation as Impartial Arbitrator Correspondence w/ Schwartz, 1982-1983 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Kheel v. Ravitch RE: redesignation as Impartial Arbitrator Correspondence Mulhearn, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Kheel v. Ravitch Court of Appeals Decision, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Kheel v Ravitch Brief of Res-Res Motion to Dismiss Appeal (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Kheel v. Ravitch Notice of Motion to Strike Material not Property in the Record + Appel. Brief, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Kheel v. Ravitch Affidavit in Support of Deferral or Denial of Respondent's Motion to Strike, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- Kheel v. Ravitch Correspondence, 1982-1986 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Kheel v. Ravitch re: Redesignation as Impartial Arbitrator correspondence, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Kheel v. Ravitch Re: Redesignation as Impartial Arbitrator correspondence, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Kheel v. Ravitch, Re: redesignation as Impartial Arbitrator Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- Kheel v. Ravitch (Folder 1), 1983 (Box 41, Folder 27)
- Kheel v. Ravitch (Folder 2), 1983 (Box 41, Folder 28)
- Kheel v. Ravitch (Folder 3), 1983 (Box 41, Folder 29)
- Kheel v. Ravitch Pleadings, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Kheel v. Ravitch Legal research, 1983-1984 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Kheel v. ravitch RE: Redesignation as Impartial Arbitrator, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Kheel v. Ravitch, RE: Redesignation as Impartial Arbitrator Copies Drafts, 1974-1982 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Kheel v. Ravitch RE: Redesignation as Impartial Arbitrator Litigation Binders, 1982-1983 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  Vol. 1 May 5 - Oct 25, 1982 and Vol. 2 Oct 27, 1982 - May 23, 1983
- Kheel v. Ravitch RE: Redesignation as Impartial Arbitrator NYC Transit Authority - TWU, 1978-1982 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Kheel v. Ravitch, RE: Redesignation as Impartial Arbitrator Freedom of Information Act, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Kheel v. Ravitch RE: Redesignation as Impartial Arbitrator Newspaper Clippings, 1982-1984 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Campaign Contributions - Clinton, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Campaign Funds RE: Carcy/Hoffa Election, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Industrial Relations Research Event Honoring TWK, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Matthew Bender + Co. RE: Kheel, Labor Law, 1987-1989 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous Kheel Personal, 1969-1978 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- TWK's Personal Info Article - The New Yorker Magazine, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- TWK General Files Photographs - Miscellaneous Photos, 2004-2005 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- TWK Personal Information Seton Hall Law School, 1999-2000 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- TWK Personal Information Speeches, 1956-2002 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- TWK Personal Information Who's Who In America, 1995-2004 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Casa Guyacan (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Casa Guayacan Photographs (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Casa Guayacan Photo Album, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Kheel, Theodore RE: Agreement with Lambrou (Pari Passu), 1984-1985 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Theodore Kheel Incorporation of Raoul Garino, Inc., 1983-1986 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Paoul Garino - Purchase of La Cocotte Restaurant, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Kheel, Theodore W. RE: Raoul Garino LA Cocotte Restaurant, Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Kheel, Theodore W. RE: Raoul Garino LA Cocotte Restaurant, Inc., Resources Industrial Bank, 1986-1987 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Kheel, Theodore W. RE: Raoul Garino LA Cocotte Restaurant, Inc., Rapid-American Corporation, 1981-2006 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Kheel, Theodore W. RE: Raoul Garino LA Cocotte Restaurant, Inc. Insurance Proposal Stockholder Agreement, 1983-1985 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- TWK The Fisher Park Avenue Company (International Paper Co.), 1978 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Kheel Tower Co. Advs North River Insurance Company, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Kheel Theodore W. People of the state of NY vs. Kheel - Traffic Ticket, 1995-2006 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- TWK Files - UN Forum on Employment, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- David Kimmel RE: Caraway Associates, Ltd., 1987 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- David Kimmel: Culinary Playhouse Premises, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Kirshner, Marc RE: Lincoln Center, 1993-2002 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Kliegl Bros. - 321 West 50th St., 1960 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Kluver, Billy The Swedish American Art Foundation, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Kluver, Billy Miscellaneous Articles, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Kochavi, Mati Bridging the Rift, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Wittrock v. KPMG Correspondence, 1997-2002 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Wittrock v. KPMG Legal Documents, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Fischer v. KPMG Peat Marwick (folder 1), 1996 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Fischer v. KPMG Peat Marwick (folder 2), 1996 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Fischer v. KPMG Peat Marwick (folder 3), 1996 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Fischer v. KPGM Peat Marwick (Folder 4), 1996 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Fischer v. KPMG Peat Marwick (folder 5), 1996 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Fischer v. KPMG Peat Marwick (Folder 6), 1995-1996 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Fischer v. KPMG Peat Marwick (folder 7), 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Kreisman, Ronald, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Kummerfeld, Elizabeth, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- K + R company Correspondence + Memos, 1977-1981 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- K + R Company Promissory Note, 1977-1979 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- K + R company Copies, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- K + R company Miscellaneous, 1976-1978 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- K + R Company Agreements, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- K + R Company Partnership Returns, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Leather Goods Union, Local No. 1 (Misc) Unions - Miscellaneous Union Matters, 1965-1989 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Legal Services Program - Local Services for the Poor - Reports, 1969-1972 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Legal Services Program - Legal Services for the Poor - reports + Great Applications, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Legal Services Program Backup Center, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Lending Tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Correspondence, 1988-2003 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Lending Tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Letters to Shareholders, 1998-2003 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- Lending Tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Bank of NY - Wealthlink Loan for Extension of Credit Secured by Margin Stock, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Lending Tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Investment with Circle Lending, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Lending Tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Amended + Restated Registration Rights Agm.t, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Lending Tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Registration Rights Agmt., 1999 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Lending Tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Stockholders Agreement, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Lending Tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Lock-Up Agreement, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Lending Tree (Wilson, Robert G.) annual Report/Prospectus/Form 10K, 2001-2003 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Lending tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Stockholders Voting Agreement, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Lending tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Stock Purchase Agreement + Schedule + Exhibits, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Lending Tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Signature Pages, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Lending Tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Series A, 8% Convertible Preferred Stock Purchase Agreement, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Lending tree Series A Financing Documents (Folder 1), 2001 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Lending Tree Series A Financing Documents (Folder 2), 2001 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Lending Tree Series A Financing Documents (Folder 3), 1998 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Lending Tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Statement of Ownership, stock Certificate (Copy), 2001-2002 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Lending tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Notice of Exercise of Registration Rights, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Lending tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Special Meeting Notices, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  May 24
- Lending tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Schedule 13 D Questionnaire/Task Fdn., 2001 (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Lending tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Cert. of Corporate Authorization to Transfer, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 18)
- Lending Tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Stock Certificate Replacement, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- Lending Tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Notice to Amendment to the Certificate of Incorporation, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 20)
- Lending Tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Background Info Consent form, Acknowledgement + Waiver/Consent + Waiver, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 21)
- Lending Tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Business Plan/Press + Analyst Citations, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 22)
- Lending Tree (Wilson, Robert G.) Pamphlets, Press Releases, Newsletter, 1999-2001 (Box 46, Folder 23)
- Leventon + Schlesinger, 1960-1961 (Box 46, Folder 24)
- Lichten, Bob Agreement w/ TWK, 1994-1998 (Box 46, Folder 25)
- National Conference on Creating Nation of Lifelong Learners, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 26)
- Link Systems International RE: Dan Koch, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Link Systems International IRS Info, 1998-1999 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Link Systems International Proposed Agreement w/ Mathworkshop.com, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Link Systems International financials, 1998-2001 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Link Systems International Sales Rep + Marketing Agreement, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Link Systems International Agreement RE: Schilit Shares, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Link Systems International Promissory Note, 1998-1999 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Link Systems International Corporate Documents, 1999-2000 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Link Systems International Sales Review, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Link systems International Business Plan, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Link systems International Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Link Systems International Fact Sheet, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Link Systems International Monthly Sales Reports (Folder 1), 2001 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  July-Nov
- Link systems International Monthly Sales Reports (Folder 2), 2001 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  Feb-July
- Little Mountain Development - correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Little Mountain Development - Tax Information, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Little Mountain Development Agreement Between Massey + Kheel, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- Little Mountain Development - Liquidation of Corporation, 1981-1984 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Little Mountain Development - Closing Costs, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Little Mountain development - Plans, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 20)
- TWK Correspondence w/ Architect Little Mountain, 1973-1976 (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Little Mountain - Corresp., 1978-1981 (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Lorant, Stefan - correspondence, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 23)
- Louant Trading Corporation, 1961 (Box 47, Folder 24)